Using language. Reading, speaking, and writing.
Andy, the Android.
I'm part of an Android football team.
About once a year we are allowed to get together to play a game of football.
I’m as big as a human.
In fact, I look like one too.
My computer chips help me to move and think like a human.
For example, I have learned to signal to my teammates in computer language to give me the ball
when I am open and have a good shot for a goal.
My first football competition was in Nagoya,
Japan several years ago.
Last year our team went to Seattle,
Washington in the USA.
We won second place.
Personally, I think the team that won first place cheated.
They had developed a new type of program just before the competition.
So we need to encourage our programmer to improve our intelligence too.
We are determined to create an even better system.
In a way our programmer is like our coach.
She programs us with all the possible moves she has seen
while watching human games.
Then she prepares reliable moves to use if a new situation arises.
In this way I can make up new moves using my "artificial intelligence".
I would really like to play against a human team,
for I have been programmed to act just like them.
After all, with the help of my electronic brain which never forgets anything,
using my intelligence is what I’m all about!